ANTHONY GORDON KRUGER

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

o DETAILS o

antman.kruger@gmail.com 061 034 0820

o LINKS o

Portfolio LinkedIn

<u>GitHub</u>

o SKILLS o

JavaScript

NextJS

ReactJS

HTML

Tailwind CSS

Java

Python

WordPress

Linux

• LANGUAGES •

English

Afrikaans

PROFILE

As a highly motivated individual with a strong foundation in web development and a bachelor's degree in Information Technology earned in 2021, I am enthusiastic about taking my career to the next level as a Full Stack Web Developer. Drawing from my successful tenure as a Retail Branch Manager, where I honed my leadership and customer centric skills, I'm excited to demonstrate how my unique blend of experience and technical knowledge makes me an ideal candidate.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Full Stack Web Developer at EZdev Solutions (PTY) ltd, International

December 2022 — Present

I am responsible for creating dynamic and user-friendly web applications, making use of a modern tech stack that includes Next.js, React.js, and Tailwind CSS. My role involves a broad spectrum of tasks, ranging from front-end development and UI/UX design to CMS integration, e-commerce solutions, database management, server-side development, version control, performance optimization, security, testing and debugging, documentation, collaboration, and continuous learning.

Full Stack Web Developer at DPTS pty ltd, International

November 2020 — December 2022

I led a web development team at DPTS, building dynamic websites and e-commerce stores for international clients. This included code migration, administration, and support of cloud-hosted environments on Microsoft Azure. This hands-on experience complemented my theoretical knowledge from my three-year bachelor's degree in information technology.

Branch Manager at The Lighting Warehouse, Pretoria

June 2018 — Present

Directing all operational aspects including distribution, customer service, human resources, administration, and sales in accordance with the company's objectives. Providing training, coaching, development, and motivation for branch personnel. Developing forecasts and financial objectives.

Sales Manager at The Lighting Warehouse, Pretoria

August 2016 — May 2018

Sales Consultant at The Lighting Warehouse, Pretoria

June 2014 — July 2016

Administrator at Precision Financial Services, Pretoria

January 2014 — April 2014

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree in information technology, Richfield Graduate Institute of Technology, Pretoria – SAQA ID: 35954

January 2019 — December 2021

National Senior Certificate, Lyttleton Manor, Pretoria

January 2006 — December 2010

1 REFERENCES

Dillon Adams from Digital Stream

dillon.adams@digitalstream.co.za · 074 155 3850

Dylan Park from The Lighting Warehouse

dylan@lightingwarehouse.co.za · 079 695 1792

Linnet Adams from Precision Financial Services

linneta@mumbi.co.za · 012 655 0618



Dillon Adams 17 July 2023

Creative Director
Digital Stream
010 023 8910
dillon.adams@digitalstream.co.za

RE: Letter of Recommendation

To whom it may concern,

Anthony Kruger was contracted to redevelop the Digital Stream website, internally we did not have the expertise or time to build the website over on a new framework and we had a number of issues with new integrations we needed to implement with regards to marketing the business. During the time of the redevelopment of the Digital Stream website, Anthony reported directly to me, the Creative Director.

It is my pleasure to recommend Anthony Kruger for the position of web developer. He is passionate about writing code and solving clients' problems through the development of creative and innovative software. He has tremendous potential that is not being fulfilled in his current position.

Anthony dedicated focus and time on this project in his spare time which he still managed to complete in an impressive two weeks. Not only did he rebuild the website over in the new framework, but he simplified and cleaned the source code for easier maintenance.

It's clear to see that Anthony is dedicated to providing quality work. He checked and rechecked the website rebuild before turning it in for presentation. He is detail oriented, and we could not find any bugs in the finished product which is exactly what we expected. In my meetings with Anthony, he easily comprehended instructions quickly and was flexible when changes needed to be made versus the original website that we had.

I hope you will consider Anthony Kruger for a job as a web developer. I am confident that he can meet any challenge you place before him, and I believe you would be exceedingly pleased with his work should you choose to hire him. Please feel free to contact me if you have questions or want to discuss Anthony's qualifications further. I can be reached at +27 74 155 3850 or via email at dillon.adams@digitalstream.co.za.

Yours sincerely,

Dillon Adams Creative Director

Director: D.C. Adams



Me certify that

ANTHONY GORDON KRUGER

(IDENTITY NO :

has complied with the requirements for BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

(WITH ELECTIVE IN SYSTEMS DEVELOPMENT)

(SAQA ID 35954: NQF 7: 380 CREDITS)

during the 2021 academic year.

STUDENT REFERENCE: HIT/02/03/ 401900582 / 207 CAMPUS: Durban Main Campus

DATE OF ISSUE: 22" Day of April 2022

DEAN OF FACULTY

GROUP CHIEF ACADEMIC REGISTRAR

DIRECTOR GROUP ACADEMIC **ADMINISTRATION**

e) ste

ISSUED WITHOUT ALTERATIONS/ERASURES.





ACADEMIC RECORD

Student Name: MR ANTHONY GORDON KRUGER

Student ID No:

Student No : 139399 /401900582

Campus

: MLA Durban

Date of Issue : 04 February 2022

	BACHEL			INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY		
(Elective: Systems Development) (SAQA ID: 35954, NQF LEVEL: 7, CREDITS 380)						
SEMESTER 1 YEAR 2019				SEMESTER 2 YEAR 2019		
	MODULES	%		MODULES	%	
1.	Information Systems 511	Credit Granted	1.	Information Systems 512	Credit Granted	
· 2.	Mathematics 511	Credit Granted	2.	Mathematics 512	Credit Granted	
3.	Networks 511	92	3.	Networks 512	92	
4.	Programming 511	Credit Granted	4.	Programming 512	Credit Granted	
5.	Web Technology 511	Credit Granted	5.	Web Technology 512	Credit Granted	
	CEMECTED 2 VID 1 D					
SEMESTER 3 YEAR 2020				SEMESTER 4 YEAR 2020		
-	MODULES	%		MODULES	%	
1.	Cloud Computing 600	91	_ 1.	Big Data & IOT 600	82	
2.	Database Systems 600	82	2.	Information Systems 622	90	
	Information Systems 621	90	3.	Internet Programming 622	84	
<u>4.</u>	Internet Programming 621	74	4.	Management Information Systems & BI 600	90	
3,	Programming 621	92	_ 5.	Programming 622	73	
	SEMESTED 5 VE	D 2021				
	SEMESTER 5 YEAR 2021 MODULES			SEMESTER 6 YEAR 2021		
1.	Cyber Security 700	%		MODULES	0/0	
2.	IT Project Management 700	91	_1.	Elective: Artificial Intelligence 700	85	
3.	Mobile App Development 700	93	2.	IT Project 700	73	
4.	Programming 731	73	3.	Programming 732	81	
5.	Elective: Programming 741	87	4,	Elective: Programming742	81	
٥,	Elective, Frogramming 741	87	5.	Work Integrated Learning 700	91	

Dr. M Kooblal

Medste

Chief Academic Registrar